The census data is not sensitive.
人口普查数据不是敏感数据
On one hand, gender and age are protected data and
尽管性别和年龄数据受到保护 并且被普遍认为是敏感数据
considered sensitive, however, the data being discussed is aggregated
但是人口普查数据合计所达到的粒度
to a granularity that does not allow for re-identification of individuals.
不能够用于对个人身份的重新鉴定
As such, storing and
因此
analyzing it on your own servers does not carry any privacy concerns.
在个人服务器上存储和分析人口普查数据不会涉及任何隐私问题
The data about how many people visit various web sites is also not sensitive,
各网站的访问人数也不是敏感数据
even if it's for a health site or a porn site.
健康网站和色情网站的访问人数也不例外
There's no way to tell who is visiting the sites based on this data.
根据这些数据无法知道访客的身份
You're only collecting the total number of visitors.
因为数据显示的仅仅是访客的总数
The glucose data could potentially be sensitive, even though it's anonymous.
血糖数据可能是潜在敏感数据 即使是匿名也不例外
The exact timestamps could be enough information to link the data to
具体的时间戳
a specific person in some extreme circumstances.
在某些极端情况下足以将数据联系到特定的人
It's pretty unlikely that anyone would actually be able to do this,
当然现实生活中鲜少有人会这样做
even if it were theoretically possible.
尽管理论上来说有这种可能性
But glucose levels are private health data, so
血糖水平作为私人的健康数据
it's important to be extra safe.
其安全性需要得到格外保护
Health data is subject to additional regulation, such as HIPAA
另外 健康数据受到 HIPAA 法案等约束
which specifies that timestamps are considered personally identifiable.
该法案明确指出通过时间戳可以辨别个人身份
Certainly if the ID you store with the data is not actually anonymous and
当然 如果随数据存储的个人身份信息没有采取匿名的形式
is possible to recover a name, an email address, or
可以据此获得个人姓名、电子邮箱地址
a phone number from it, then this would be sensitive data.
或者电话号码 那么这些数据就是敏感数据
The game data is not sensitive.
游戏数据不是敏感数据
Again, it's possible that you could recover the person's identity from
同样 你可能会获得用户个人信息
details such as the time stamps, but that's not a very likely outcome.
比如通过时间戳等细节 但是这种可能性并不大
Moreover, since game data is not sensitive, even if someone could recover
而且 由于游戏数据为非敏感数据 即使有人获得了这些细节
the details, that would be low risk for the participant.
对参与者来说 风险也是很低的
The sales data for the shopping site broken down by zip
按照 zip 编号细分的购物网站的销售数据
code is not sensitive, because the totals are stored for a zip code.
不是敏感数据 因为总数是以 zip 编号进行储存的
Typically, a zip code has enough individuals active in that area that
通常来说 一个 zip 编号中包含的活跃在某特定区域的个人
information in that level of granularity does not have a re-identification risk.
其粒度所含信息不足以构成重新鉴定个人身份的风险
A better guideline, though, rather than using zip code,
与其使用 zip 编号 更好的一个原则
would be to ensure that there are enough data points to guarantee that the data
是确保有足够的数据点
is sufficiently anonymized.
来保证数据的匿名化
The credit card data is definitely sensitive
信用卡数据无疑是敏感的
If you entered your credit card number on a shopping site,
如果需要在购物网站上输入信用卡卡号
you would definitely expect that site to be storing the data securely.
那么务必确定该网站能够安全地存储这些信息